Hello friends welcome to our
youtube channel so today we will discuss
about a very big news ICICI
Lombard Bharti AXA has been confirmed to be worth
27 crores and
ICICI Lombard will become the
third largest insurance company in India
after this deal the most
special thing about this deal is that the shareholders
of Bharti AXA will get the shares of ICICI Lombard
and the biggest advantage of this deal will be for
Lombard that it will be able to expand its business by using the Indian
Army's business and
their old partnership
and will be able to grow as quickly as possible
so there is a full possibility of this stock being a hit keep
watching this news and thank you